Clayton Moulynox

- http://www.auth0.com
- http://twitter.com/claytonhm/
- http://www.moulynox.com/

SUMMARY

My professional development over the past 15 years has been less than conventional, but rather driven by a commitment to learning from others, throwing myself in the deep end, an ability to think creatively and strategically and an urge to challenge the status-quo. I'm constantly thinking outside the box to drive innovation and success in the teams I work within or lead.

Passionate about - and always looking for opportunities to be involved in - new small business ventures and startups, mentoring young people in business and sharing great ideas. Specialties: Trusted advisor at scale within the SMB IT community; speaking the language of the customer; trying something different; highly developed presentation and communication skills; advanced IT skills and understanding of technology concepts; Small business management; sales management, strategy and execution; marketing strategy and execution; channel development; business development; franchise system development & management; writing; creative concept development.

SKILLS

- Cloud Computing
- New Business Development
- Strategy
- Marketing Strategy
- Go-to-market Strategy
- Team Leadership
- Business Development
- Managed Services
- Channel Sales
- Account Management
- Partner Management
- Business Strategy
- Multi-channel Marketing
- Lead Generation
- Solution Selling
- Sales Operations
- Sales
- Market Analysis
- Product Marketing
- Influence Others
- Professional Services Software Industry
- Writing

- Strategic Partnerships
- Channel Partners
- Sales Management
- Channel Strategy
- Small Business
- Social Media
- Small Business IT Solutions
- Demand Generation
- Sales Presentations
- Microsoft Technologies
- Customer Engagement
- Networking
- Integration
- Business Alliances
- Marketing
- Public Speaking
- Sales Process
- Small Business Marketing
- Trusted Advisor
- Product Demonstration
- Sales Enablement
- Technical Presentations

EXPERIENCE

Auth0

04 / 2015 - Present

Director of Partner Success

Building a global partner channel and driving partner success at Auth0.com.

Microsoft 03 / 2013 - 04 / 2015

Partner Channel Development Manager

My responsibility is the recruitment, activation and enablement at scale of our breadth partner eco-system across Australia with a focus on bringing our partners and mutual small & medium business customers in to the "new era" of Microsoft.

I bring together deep understanding of Microsoft's products and solutions (across onpremises, private cloud and public cloud) with an equally deep understanding of the SMB market opportunities and dynamics in Australia to the benefit of Microsoft partners.

Microsoft 09 / 2010 - 03 / 2013

Partner Territory Manager

Responsibility to build partner eco-system and meet strategic KPIs within VIC, SA & WA across public cloud (Office 365, Intune, CRM Online), private cloud (SPLA) and on-premises (Open License) businesses aligned to SMB customer segment. - Being a key influencer, capable of motivating senior executives in our distributors and partners within my territory to focus and invest against these key technology solution areas. - Reseller discovery, profiling, recruit, and activation through technical solutions training, sales coaching & marketing planning. - Increase reseller reach through scale distribution partnerships, actively engaging in execution of distribution sales, marketing and technical readiness within territory. - Strengthen reseller community and satisfaction through social media engagement; 1:many events, 1:few focus groups and 1:1 coaching with key influencers and strategic partners. - Customer targeting, monitor broad market opportunities within territory, demand generation through 1:many presentations, customer satisfaction through building trust via scale engines such as social media and connecting to Microsoft partner ecosystem.

Microsoft 01 / 2010 - 09 / 2010

Channel Development Manager - Commercial

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES - Drive transactional partner channel readiness (training) and marketing strategies to stimulate technology adoption and sales activation, achieving key channel recruitment and development targets. MAJOR ACHIEVEMENTS - Led Office 2010 launch to Microsoft Partners Australia wide. - "Throw This Away" channel marketing initiative winner of ADMA award (http://ldrv.ms/1x6cxFo)

Small Business Daily Blog

03 / 2009 - 08 / 2010

Expert

Pro bono contributor offering insights into business sales, marketing & growth. Wrote second highest viewed article on site to date, "Don't Rely on Your IT Guy" http://smallbizexperts.wordpress.com/2009/05/14/dont-rely-on-your-it-guy/, which gained considerable industry exposure and comment from companies including Kaseya and lead to

speaking engagements with organisations such as MSP Mentor http://www.mspmentor.net/2009/11/22/join-us-australia-managed-services-webcast/.

Evolve IT Australia

01 / 2006 - 12 / 2009

General Manager (& Managing Director - WA)

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES - Charged with developing the company's business in WA from the ground up and the ongoing day-to-day management. Includes recruiting employees, setting up key business partnerships and a continuing hands on approach to finding new business. -

Charged with implementing the strategic and operational management of the company as a whole (both VIC and WA branches) including establishing, reviewing and refining business systems and processes (in line with ISO9001 quality systems standard) to cater for growth and increase profitability, whilst maintaining exceptional service delivery to clients. - Analyse group financials, measuring profitability of key business areas and developing goals and strategies to improve. - Provide ongoing advice, strategy and direction to other key stakeholders in the business in the areas of sales and marketing, and execution of a sales, marketing and PR activities. - Set and measure group goals ensuring that business strategy and process is in line with achieving these. MAJOR ACHIEVEMENTS: - Won 4 industry awards during time as GM, including Microsoft Wordlwide Small Business Specialist Partner of the Year 2009 (http://bit.ly/f4z3IH) - Developed the WA business in 2006 from scratch. - Steered the group through change to build an internal structure focusing on an MSP business model. - Providing the key sales and operational strategy, including internal systems and procedures based on ITIL and Microsoft Operations Framework.

Evolve IT Australia

10 / 2002 - 12 / 2005

Product and Business Development Manager

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: - Development of new I.T. infrastructure management and user system support solutions and service offerings. - Provide strategic technology consulting services to client executives, recommending system improvements, bespoke application development and long term technology strategy - Identify target markets and develop new business from these markets. - Develop recurring revenue based business. - Provide sales and marketing strategy and advice. - Supervise small service delivery team. MAJOR ACHIEVEMENTS: - Developed and introduced "service contracts" to client base who had traditionally received break-fix IT support. By end of 2005, annual service contracts were \$400k per annum. - Managed the process of successfully achieving Microsoft Gold Certified status. - Significantly grew the company's client base in the SMB market - Made part of management team and responsible for marketing plans and setting KPI's and business goals

Hire Intelligence

05 / 2000 - 09 / 2002

Franchise Manager

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES - Improving and/or developing franchise system policies and procedures focussed on operational efficiency through the use of information technology systems. - Responsible for directly providing franchisee's with operational support (or outsourcing support as required) across information systems. - Initial business training and ongoing development of new Franchisees. Ongoing support and training of existing franchisees in the areas of technology, sales, marketing and operations. - Monitoring of Franchisee satisfaction, Franchisees' sales activity and performance against budget as well as changes in technology, the industry, competitor activity and the market environment. -Develop and promoting head office marketing strategies to Franchisees and assisting them with tailored marketing strategies within their own territory. - Complete quarterly reviews of franchisee's businesses ensuring compliance to systems and procedures by auditing information technology systems and conducting a physical inspection of premises and staff procedural duties. - Market analysis of other countries to sell franchises in. Franchise analysis includes IT trends, commercial laws and regulations with respect to franchising, competitor analysis and potential marketing opportunities. MAJOR ACHIEVEMENTS - Sole trainer for 6week franchise training course for new UK franchisees, held in London, UK. All trainees achieved high pass rates and commenced trading as franchisees. - Developed and was ongoing editor of "Inside Intelligence", the first quarterly publication for Hire Intelligence franchisees worldwide. - Developed extranet concept and content to streamline

communications and enhance support for the franchise chain worldwide. The extranet was nominated as a finalist at the WAITTA awards in 2002.

Bedrock Computer Services

03 / 1997 - 12 / 1999

Technical Specialist

- Provided technical integration and support services to primarily SMB customers.
- Contracted out to TABCorp to provide help desk services and be a vendor support representative located onsite.

EDUCATION

Swinburne University of Technology

1996 - 1997

Social Science; Media & Journalism major

Ringwood Secondary College

1990 - 1995

College Prefect 1995; Student Representative on School Council 1994.

INTERESTS

New technology, emerging business ideas, the internet, writing, AFL, photography

CERTIFICATIONS

Developing Innovative Ideas for New Companies: The First Step in Entrepreneurship

01 / 2014

University of Maryland offered through Coursera · License: QHDTMTBS7Q